(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
HOLOLIVE INDONESIA SECOND GENERATION
KUREIJI OLLIE PRESENT
Hah...
Huh...
(Laughs)
Gemas banget sih~
You're so cute~
Kagetan gitu?
You get startled so easily?
Ini kan yang kamu nanti-nantikan?
Wasn't this what you were waiting for?
Bisa bicara sama...
To be able to talk to...
Oshi?
your oshi?
Ngapain tuh mencet tombol back?
Why are you frantically pressing the back button?
Jangan-jangan...
Don't tell me...
kamu nggak suka Ollie ngomong langsung begini?
you dislike Ollie talking directly like this?
Ehh~? Kenapa hp-nya kok dimatiin sih?
Ehh~? Why'd you turn off the phone?
Kamu tuh sah... beneran nggak suka ngomong sama Ollie ya?
You really don't want to talk to me huh?
Keseruan yang baru akan dimulai sekarang~
The fun is just about to begin~
Darling~
存在証明 愛だって 愛だって 吐いたって
Proof of existence, even if it's love, even if I vomit love
嗚呼 寝転んゴロンて 嫌ん嫌ん
Ah, rolling around, no no
プリティプリティ ダイエットDAY
Pretty pretty diet DAY
曖昧一回楽に
Vaguely once comfortably
アイマイミー快楽に
I my me in pleasure
病み悪化してんだって
My sickness is getting worse
愛だ恋だ何だってんだ
Love, romance, what is it anyway?
生命線は 愛だって 愛だ 嘆いたって
The lifeline is love, lamenting that it's love
嗚呼 でも無いこうでも無いな
Ah, it's not this, it's not that
寂しい寂しいナンセンスDAY
Lonely lonely nonsense DAY
いっそ密会ラフに
Rather have a rough secret meeting
節操無い解 LOVE ME
Unprincipled answer LOVE ME
溺れ奴隷
Drowning slave
踊れ踊れ 暴れだ
Dance, dance, rampage
なにもない なにもない
Nothing, nothing
私なにもない
I have nothing
変われない 変われない
Can't change, can't change
私変われない
I can't change
分からない 分からない
Don't understand, don't understand
「わかる」分からない
"I understand" I don't understand
はーい 目元以外は隠して
Yess, hide everything but the eyes
ダダダダダダ ダリダリダーリン
Da-da-da-da-da-da Dari-dari-darling
ダーリン
Darling
Funny
はい冴えない愛情論で
Yes, with a dull love theory
おねだり
Begging
ダダダダ ダリン 脳裏
Da-da-da-da Darling, in my mind
DIRTY & DIRTY
会いたい衝動 埋めてよ
Bury this impulse to see you
ダダダーリン
Da-da-darling
無 無 無 無 無 無
Nothing nothing nothing
無い無い清純 感情が行ったり来たり
No purity, emotions going back and forth
無 無 無 無 無 無
Nothing nothing nothing
無い無い純情 感傷で
No pure heart, with sentimentality
ダダダダ
Da-da-da-da
ダダダダ ダーリンだ
Da-da-da-da it's Darling
愛だ喘いだ って
Gasping that it's love
まあ ネコロンゴロンで ニャンニャン
Well, rolling around like a cat, meow meow
食い意地 食い意地 ダイエットDAY
Gluttony gluttony diet DAY
もう精一杯で積み
Already checked out at my limit
暴論 正解で無理
Outrageous theory, correct answer is impossible
病み垢してんだって
Using a sick account
承認 承認 絶対だ
Approval approval is absolute
なにもない なにもない
Nothing, nothing
私なにもない
I have nothing
はしたない はしたない
Immodest, immodest
私はしたない
I am immodest
分からない 分からない
Don't understand, don't understand
「わかる」分からない
"I understand" I don't understand
はーい 自撮りは全部加工して
Yess, edit all the selfies
ダダダダダダ ダリダリダーリン
Da-da-da-da-da-da Dari-dari-darling
FUNNY
はい絶えない愛情論で
Yes, with unending love theory
冷めたり
Cooling down
ダダダダ ダリン 無理
Da-da-da-da Darling impossible
DIRTY & DIRTY
会いたい衝動 止めてよ
Stop this impulse to see you
ダダダーリン
Da-da-darling
踊れ
Dance
叫べ
Scream
踊れ
Dance
ルラッパッパ
Lu-la-pa-pa
踊れ
Dance
唄え
Sing
踊れ
Dance
ルラッパッパ
Lu-la-pa-pa
もうドッキンドッキン脳
Already thumping thumping brain
しんど期 しんど期 ロー
Tough times, tough times, low
はーい 素顔は全部無くして
Yess, lose all of your real face
ダダダダダダ ダリダリダーリン
Da-da-da-da-da-da Dari-dari-darling
FUNNY
どうしようもない感情論に
Laughing at the hopeless emotional theory
わらったり
Laughing
ダダダダ ダリン 脳裏
Da-da-da-da Darling, in my mind
DIRTY & DIRTY
会いたい衝動 埋めてよ
Bury this impulse to see you
ダダダーリン
Da-da-darling
無 無 無 無 無 無
Nothing nothing nothing
無い無い反応 返答を期待したり
No reaction, expecting a reply
無 無 無 無 無 無
Nothing nothing nothing
無い無い妄想 感傷で
No delusion, with sentimentality
ダダダダ ダーリン
Da-da-da-da Darling
無い無い純情 感傷で
No pure heart, with sentimentality
ダダダダ ダーリン
Da-da-da-da Darling
ねぇ
Hey
だ
Dar
あ
l
り
i
ん
ng
けーたいみしてよ
Show me your phone.
待ちわびている大通り
The main street is waiting impatiently.
目眩しそうな人混み
A dizzying crowd.
くるり回ったヒロビン
Spinning around, heroine.
立ち止まってるボーボー
Standing still, boy.
しまい切れてない表情
An expression you can't quite hide.
どこ見てるのボーボー
Where are you looking, boy?
知らない
I don't know.
今何
What now?
目と目止まった合図
The signal when our eyes met.
ロングのロリーズ
Long Lollies.
「あとでね」
"Later, okay?"
黒文字
Spicebush.
隠してもムダね
It's useless to hide it.
けけけケータイみしてよ
Sho-sho-sho-show me your phone.
今から
Right now.
けけけケータイみしてよ
Sho-sho-sho-show me your phone.
今から
Right now.
けけけケータイみしてよ
Sho-sho-sho-show me your phone.
今から
Right now.
ねえ今から
Hey, right now.
ねえいいでしょ
Hey, it's fine, right?
ケータイみしてよ
Show me your phone.
拒んでるの予想通り
Refusing, just as I expected.
だって賭けたこの試み
Because this attempt I wagered on.
くるり回ったヒロビン
Spinning around, heroine.
立ち止まっていないで
Don't stand still.
怒ったりしないでよ
Don't get angry.
I need チュッチュッチュッチュ
I need chu-chu-chu-chu.
いらない
I don't need it.
苛立ち
Irritation.
使い古しの愛も
Worn-out love too.
言い訳達も
And the excuses.
画面じゃなく
Not the screen,
ここ見て
look here.
取り上げるからね
I'm taking it away, okay?
けけけケータイみしてよ
Sho-sho-sho-show me your phone.
今から
Right now.
けけけケータイみしてよ
Sho-sho-sho-show me your phone.
今から
Right now.
けけけケータイみしてよ
Sho-sho-sho-show me your phone.
今から
Right now.
ねえ今から
Hey, right now.
ねえいいでしょ
Hey, it's fine, right?
ケータイかしてよ
Lend me your phone.
今から
Right now.
けけけケータイかしてよ
Le-le-le-lend me your phone.
今から
Right now.
けけけケータイかしてよ
Le-le-le-lend me your phone.
今から
Right now.
ねえ今すぐ
Hey, right now.
渡しなさい
Hand it over.
ねえいいでしょ
Hey, it's fine, right?
ケータイみしてよ
Show me your phone.
Oh! You woke up!
Hi, good morning...
Did you have a good sleep?
Oh... here?
This is my room!
What was that?
Looks a bit different?
Ehehe~ I guess you found out.
I, um, prepared this room just for us.
'Cause it's a special room!
Yeah, um, I wanted to make our memory...
...as special as possible...
...so I worked really hard!
And I prepared the perfect scenery just for us.
I even transported you here while you were still asleep.
I... I just didn't want...
...I just didn't want you to be tired, is all.
I just love you so much that...
...I want these feelings to properly reach you.
Huh? What's wrong?
I'm not like my usual self?
Hehe~ You're so silly~
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Ah! Wait! Don't go!
Where are you going?
Eh... Wow. I can't believe you ran away like that...
But you were so cute when you were so shy!
指切りげんまん ホラでも吹いたら
Pinky promise, if I tell a lie...
針でもなんでも飲ませていただき
Make me swallow needles or anything.
Monday
It doesn't matter if it's Sunday
この世で一番変わることのない
The one thing in this world that never changes...
愛をくれるのはだれ
Who is it that gives me love?
No need to ask cause it's my darling
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last.
あなたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than parting with you like this,
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die.
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I prefer you over three meals a day.
あんたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than parting with you like this,
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die.
それでも時々浮つく My Heart
Yet sometimes, my heart wavers.
死んでも治らな治してみせます baby
Even death won't fix it? I'll fix it for sure, baby.
Yeah I ain't nothin but ya baby
失って初めて気がつくなんて
To only realize it after losing it,
そんなダサいこともうしたないのよ goodbye
I don't want to do anything so lame anymore. Goodbye.
Oh Don't you ever say ByeBye
Eh, eh, yeah
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last.
あなたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than parting with you like this,
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die.
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I prefer you over three meals a day.
あんたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than parting with you like this,
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die.
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last.
あなたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than parting with you like this,
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die.
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I prefer you over three meals a day.
あんたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than parting with you like this,
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die.
それでも時々浮つく My Heart
Yet sometimes, my heart wavers.
そんなダサいのはもう要らないのよ ByeBye
I don't need anything that lame anymore. ByeBye.
I'll always stick with ya my baby
ねえ
Hey.
アナタには見えぬ事ばかり
There's so much you can't see.
アタシは見ている事
That I can see clearly.
知らないの？
Didn't you know?
背中につけられた
Marked on your back,
誰かのキスの跡
is the trace of someone's kiss.
一人じゃ買う訳の無いそれも
And that thing you'd never buy alone,
見て見ぬフリなだけ
I'm just pretending not to see.
じゃあね
See ya.
笑っちまう程に
It's laughable,
キュートなカノジョ
what a cute girlfriend.
常時奔放狂気短気
Always wild, crazy, and short-tempered.
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if I yell, one look and I'm struck.
洗脳完了女上手
Brainwashing complete, she's good at this.
愛していいのさ
You can love me.
強く愛していいのさ
You can love me strongly.
ねえ精神から全身まで
Hey, from spirit to whole body,
表面から内面まで
from surface to inside,
脳天から先端まで知りたいの
from brain to toe tip, I want to know it all.
それから最近聞いた音楽から
Also, from the music you listened to lately,
散財した総額まで
to the total amount you splurged,
完全把握しないと気が済まないわ
I won't be satisfied unless I grasp it all.
とやかく言ったって実際の所は
Whatever you say, actually,
その眼中アタシ何割くらいに
how much of your focus,
なってるの？
is really on me?
はぁ隠してないで
Haa, don't hide it,
確信を頂戴
give me certainty.
サレド黙して語らず
Yet you stay silent and say nothing.
バイバイ
Bye bye.
困っちまう程に
It's troubling,
キュートなカノジョ
what a cute girlfriend.
容姿淡麗耽美甘美
Beautiful, aesthetic, sweet looks.
身勝手だって泣くシックな素振り
Crying selfishly with a chic attitude.
瞬時酩酊女冥利
Instant intoxication, a woman's charm.
愛しちまうのさ
I end up loving you.
されど愛しちまうのさ
Still, I end up loving you.
過去を喰らう程に
Enough to devour the past,
ポップなエイジ
pop age.
排気ガスから香るコロン
Cologne smelling from exhaust gas.
騙し奪われる恋でもいいの
I don't mind a love where I'm deceived and stolen.
だって彼処へは
Because over there...
めちゃくちゃ可愛いでしょ？
I'm super cute, right?
笑っちまう程に
It's laughable,
キュートなカノジョ
what a cute girlfriend.
常時奔放狂気短気
Always wild, crazy, and short-tempered.
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if I yell, one look and I'm struck.
洗脳完了女上手
Brainwashing complete, she's good at this.
困っちまう程に
It's troubling,
キュートなカノジョ
what a cute girlfriend.
容姿淡麗耽美甘美
Beautiful, aesthetic, sweet looks.
身勝手だって泣くシックな素振り
Crying selfishly with a chic attitude.
瞬時酩酊女冥利
Instant intoxication, a woman's charm.
愛していいのさ
You can love me.
強く愛していいのさ
You can love me strongly.
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
The night is just beginning, Bunny Girl.
誘惑される鼓動に
By the heartbeat that seduces you,
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に
by the conflict that bursts open,
愛を乾杯
a toast to love,
伝えられなくても
even if I can't convey it.
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of love, Bunny Girl.
誰かを穿って
Piercing through someone,
澄んだ君の目を孕んで
pregnant with your clear eyes.
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Come on, carve out a pretentious step.
仕事帰りの疲れは
The fatigue on your way home from work,
私と、このグラスに
leave it with me and this glass.
さあ 自分好みに縋って
Come on, cling to your own preferences.
世間に対する気持ち
Your feelings towards society,
私に注いでみない？
why don't you pour them into me?
ありがちなラブソングでも
Even in a typical love song,
愛が込められてるの
there is love poured into it.
それでも汚れるのね
Even so, we get dirty, don't we?
君を見れば分かるの
I can tell just by looking at you.
下を向く君の目を
Your eyes looking down,
無理やり剥ぐ事はしない
I won't forcibly pry them open.
だからそんな顔せず手を差し伸べて
So don't make that face, reach out your hand.
ほら 夜の始まりさ
Look, the night is beginning.
Bunny Girl 誘惑される
Bunny Girl, seduced...
鼓動に弾け飛ぶ
...by the heartbeat, bursting open...
葛藤に愛を
...love to the conflict...
乾杯 伝えられなくても
...cheers, even if I can't convey it.
恋の始まりさ
It's the beginning of love.
Bunny Girl 誰かを
Bunny Girl, piercing...
穿って澄んだ
...someone, pregnant...
君の目を孕んで
...with your clear eyes.
君の愛を知った気でハイになっていて
Getting high feeling like I knew your love,
感度去っていて毎度泣いていてさ
losing sensitivity and crying every time.
それくらいがいいんでしょ
That's about right, isn't it?
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Come on, carve out a pretentious step.
君の顔色今では
Your complexion now,
マシになってきてるから
it's getting better.
Ba-du-wa, ba-du-wa...
君に委ねるわ Bunny Girl
I'll leave it to you, Bunny Girl.
私をあげるわ
I'll give you myself.
Bunny Girl 誘惑される
Bunny Girl, seduced...
鼓動に弾け飛ぶ
...by the heartbeat, bursting open...
葛藤に愛を
...love to the conflict...
乾杯 伝えられてるはず
...cheers, it should be conveyed.
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
The night is just beginning, Bunny Girl.
誰かを穿って
Piercing through someone,
澄んだ君の目を
pregnant with your clear eyes...
孕んで
...
Ba-du-wa, ba-du-wa...
Dor! Wa!
There you are! I was looking everywhere for you.
Kamu nggak bilang kalau kita bakal main petak umpet~
You didn't tell me we were going to play hide and seek~
Ternyata kamu ada di neon stage, ya!
Turns out you're at the neon stage!
Jadi gimana? Cantik nggak neon stagenya?
So how is it? Is the neon stage pretty?
Ollie yang siapin, nih! Keren kan, neonnya banyak banget!
Ollie prepared this! Cool right? There's so much neon!
Pas kamu lagi sembunyi tadi, Ollie juga ganti baju.
While you were hiding earlier, Ollie also changed clothes.
Loh~ Imut nggak~?
Oh~ Cute right~?
Hehe~ Sebenernya masih banyak yang Ollie siapin buat kamu~
Hehe~ Actually there's still a lot Ollie prepared for you~
Jadi kita udahan ya main petak umpetnya~
So let's finish playing hide and seek~
Hah? Nggak mau?
Huh? You don't want to?
Eh, kamu, tuh...
Eh, you...
Sejak sampe di sini, tingkah kamu aneh banget, deh...
Since arriving here, your behavior has been really weird...
Since getting here, you've been acting really weird...
You're just... standing over there and... I just don't understand.
You've been trying to get my attention...
...by liking my posts and commenting on them...
Isn't this what you wanted?
You... You love me, right?
Don't you want to spend more time with me?
Why are you not accepting my feelings?
You're supposed to be happy, but...
...you're acting so strange...
Eh! Bentar! Chotto! Matte!
Eh! Wait! Wait! Wait!
君のサシュが効いてんだみょん
Your scent is working on me, myon.
ah-ahh, ah-ahh...
どんだけ泣いたかわかんないやいや
I don't know how much I cried, no no.
つら、サボりっぱ
Painful, slacking off.
ぽっかり空いて埋まらないやいや
Gaping open, won't fill up, no no.
ほしい、ラブぴった
I want it, love fits perfect.
ちゅちゅちゅ中途な出会いじゃ刺さんないや
A half-hearted encounter won't pierce me.
やっぱり無理かもバタンキュー
Maybe it's impossible after all, thud.
げっそりハートが治んないやいや
My emaciated heart won't heal, no no.
出してよすぐ処方箋
Issue me a prescription right now.
サヨナラの棘
The thorn of goodbye...
なんで抜けないの
...why won't it come out?
君の代わりのヒトガタが
A doll to replace you...
全然見つからない
...can't be found at all.
Oh サッドガール・セックス、ぱぱん、ウブの出棺
Oh Sad Girl Sex, pa-pan, the coffin of innocence.
知ってどんな想いだけな
Do you know what kind of feeling this is?
誰かと寝ても寂しさが発火
Sleeping with someone else just ignites the loneliness.
君のサシュが効いてんだみょん
Your scent is working on me, myon.
Oh サッドガール・セックス、ぱぱん、ラブの接待
Oh Sad Girl Sex, pa-pan, love's hospitality.
きっとまた会えるなんてさ
Saying we'll surely meet again...
思い出の君に食い尽くされっこ
Being devoured by the memory of you.
君のサシュが効いてんだみょん
Your scent is working on me, myon.
ah-ahh, ah-ahh...
ねえマンガ返してよ
Hey, give my manga back.
最新話であのキャラ死んじゃったよ
That character died in the latest chapter, you know.
教えてくれたバンドメンバー
The band member you told me about...
クスリで捕まっちゃったよ
...got arrested for drugs.
一緒に居たこと消えないやいや
The fact we were together won't disappear, no no.
全部が二人だった
Everything was about the two of us.
きっと君は今誰かと居るの
Surely you're with someone else right now.
あたしだけが課金中
I'm the only one still paying.
Oh サッドガール・セックス、ぱぱん、ウブの出棺
Oh Sad Girl Sex, pa-pan, the coffin of innocence.
嫉妬辛くてエンバッてら
Jealousy is painful, I'm stalling.
上書きがしたいどうしてくれんの
I want to overwrite it, why won't you let me?
愛のガチャガチャ天井はない
Love's gacha has no ceiling.
Oh サッドガール・セックス、ぱぱん、ラブの没収
Oh Sad Girl Sex, pa-pan, confiscation of love.
ちょっとエグすぎない本当さ
Isn't that a bit too harsh? Really.
涙の跡に狂気が走った
Madness ran through the tracks of my tears.
愛のガチャガチャ天井はない
Love's gacha has no ceiling.
もしもが叶う
If 'what ifs' came true...
素敵世界ならば
...in a wonderful world...
君はサヨナラ取り下げを
...you would withdraw your goodbye...
検討加速しちゃう
...and accelerate your consideration.
Oh サッドガール・セックス、ぱぱん、ウブの出棺
Oh Sad Girl Sex, pa-pan, the coffin of innocence.
なんでこんな終わってんだろ
Why is it so over?
誰かと寝たら埋められるような
Is it the level of love that can be filled...
レベルの愛だ？ そんなんじゃない
...by sleeping with someone else? It's not.
Oh サッドガール・セックス、ぱぱん、ラブでぺっちゃん
Oh Sad Girl Sex, pa-pan, flattened by love.
恋いまでも思ってんだわ
I still think of it as love.
期待よりの地獄 もう戻れないの
A hell closer than expected, I can't go back anymore.
君のサシュが効いてんだみょん
Your scent is working on me, myon.
探せゾッコン
Search for deep love.
だめだめはあ
No good, no good, haa.
揺らせ絶頂
Shake the climax.
あせあせはあ
Sweat, sweat, haa.
探せゾッコン
Search for deep love.
だめだめはあ
No good, no good, haa.
君の絶叫
Your scream.
効いてんだみょん
Is working on me, myon.
檻の中あたしの愛…猫
Inside the cage is my beloved... cat.
おかえりなさい君ににゃお
Welcome home, meow to you.
悪い子ね穢れたお身体で
Bad boy, with your dirty body.
行きはよいよい帰りは怖い
Going is easy, returning is scary.
愛は知らない愛猫さん
The beloved cat who knows no love.
間抜けな愛…
Stupid love...
…今日とかそりゃ結構
...today? That's fine.
睨めっこほらバレバレでもそう
Staring contest, see, it's obvious, but yeah.
なんでお仕置きだ自己嫌悪
Why is it punishment? Self-loathing.
君はあたしだけの愛猫だにゃん
You are my only beloved cat, meow.
好きになる 好きになる
Falling in love, falling in love.
ドンドン好きになる
Falling more and more in love.
好きになるね
Falling in love, aren't you?
愛して
Love me.
可愛いね 首輪つけてにゃお
You're cute, let's put a collar on you, meow.
大切に愛でてあげるにゃお
I'll cherish and adore you, meow.
檻の中の子猫ちゃん
My little kitten in the cage.
愛のロンド さあ踊りましょう
Let's dance the rondo of love.
喉鳴らし擦り寄って
Purring and rubbing close.
ほらどうぞ
Here you go.
睨めっこ あら甘えん坊さんね
Staring contest? Oh, you spoiled child.
そっぽを向いてもそりゃ結構
Even if you look away, that's fine too.
君はあたしだけの愛猫さ
You are my one and only beloved cat.
ドンドン好きになる
Falling more and more in love.
好きになる
Falling in love.
愛して
Love me.
ドンドン好きになる
Falling more and more in love.
好きになる
Falling in love.
好きになるね
Falling in love, right?
愛して
Love me.
逃げられやしないとわかってる
I know you can't run away.
一生の愛が欲しいの
I want a lifetime of love.
愛して
Love me.
最期死んで黙って君は
In the end, you'll die and fall silent,
愛猫さん
Mr. Beloved Cat.
Hello? Kamu di mana?
Hello? Where are you?
Where are you?
Ish, keluar dong!
Ugh, come out!
Come out!
Katanya udahan main petak umpetnya?
Didn't you say hide and seek was over?
Kamu ke mana coba...
Where did you go...
Gosh, where could you be?
Ayo tunjukin dirimu!
Come on, show yourself!
Show yourself!
Beneran deh, ngasih kerjaan aja ya kamu...
Seriously, you're just making work for me...
Hah, I can't believe that you would make me look for you like this.
Ah!
Ketemu!
Found you!
I found you!
Jangan ke mana-mana lagi, ya?
Don't go anywhere else, okay?
Don't go anywhere now.
言葉ひとつ香る 君のその髪が
With a single word, the scent of your hair...
僕の心を踊らせたんです
Has made my heart dance.
靡くだけ 今は それだけで
Just swaying, right now, just that...
この身 屈めますから
I will bow my body down.
Hey hey hey
Midnight光線 Darling
Midnight Ray Darling.
堪えきれぬ欲望に任せて
Giving in to uncontrollable desire.
Midnight光線 Darling
Midnight Ray Darling.
僕に仕える気になったら
If you feel like serving me.
Ah 願うは三度の絶頂を
Ah, I wish for three climaxes.
胸の中で至る
Reaching it within my heart.
今宵も僕らは繁栄のために
Tonight, for the sake of our prosperity...
愛を放つ
We release our love.
抗いの呟きとは裏腹に
Contrary to your murmurs of resistance.
身体は嬉しそうに動いたんです
Your body moved happily.
この翼に輪を付けるかは
Whether to put a ring on these wings...
僕ら次第ですから
Is up to us.
真面目ですかな
Are you serious?
淫らですかな
Or are you lewd?
Hey hey hey
Midnight光線 Darling
Midnight Ray Darling.
愛と欲に純白を求めて
Seeking purity in love and lust.
Midnight光線 Darling
Midnight Ray Darling.
僕を拒む気になっても
Even if you feel like rejecting me.
Ah 願うは三度の絶頂を
Ah, I wish for three climaxes.
胸の中で至る
Reaching it within my heart.
零れる涙が飽和して
Overflowing tears saturate everything.
僕は今に果てる
I will perish soon.
その溢れた吐息の原因なんだって？
What is the cause of that overflowing sigh?
一体どこからいったって？
Where on earth did it come from?
ドキドキなんだって？
You say your heart is pounding?
よろめく恐怖が原因なんだって？
Is faltering fear the cause?
それでも君ならいいんだって
Even so, if it's you, it's fine.
さらに
Furthermore...
Ah 願うは三度の絶頂を
Ah, I wish for three climaxes.
胸の中で至る
Reaching it within my heart.
今宵も僕らは繁栄の
Tonight, for the sake of our prosperity...
ために
For that sake...
ねえあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know.
君が一人知ってるの知ってるよ
You're all alone. I know it, I know.
ビクンビクン震えてさ
Trembling and shaking,
恋も留まりなんだわ
Love is at a stalemate too.
正直に言っちゃいなよ
Just say it honestly.
バレてるんだし言っちゃいなよ
It's obvious anyway, so just say it.
効いてんの？
Is it working?
グズグズ恥ずかしい
Whining is embarrassing,
みんな隠しているだけ
Everyone is just hiding it.
ムフッ
Muhu.
うーわ！おねがい君が欲しいの
Uwwa! Please, I want you!
慰めさせてシェイクシェイク
Let me comfort you, Shake Shake.
愛の才能で
With my talent for love.
泣いてくれなきゃ枯れてしまう
If you don't cry for me, I'll wither.
濡れていたいねえいいでしょう？
I want to stay wet, hey, it's okay right?
ダメ取って飲み干したいん
It's no good, I want to drink it all up,
だだだってば
I said D-D-D!
うーわ！
Uwwa!
ねえあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know.
君が一人悔しがってんの知ってるよ
I know you're alone and frustrated. I know.
ズクンズクン高まるよ
Throb, throb, it's rising.
君を推すことは止めない
I won't stop pushing for you.
ねえあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know.
君はできる子知ってるよ
You're a capable kid. I know.
辛い時は弱いくらいで丁度いい
When it's tough, being weak is just right.
あたしそれでも好きだよ
I still like you even then.
君が病める時も
Even when you are sick,
あたしそばにいるわ
I will be by your side.
いつも見守っているわ
I will always be watching over you.
そうよ怖くないのよ
That's right, it's not scary.
あぁ
Aah...
うーわ！おねがい君が欲しいの
Uwwa! Please, I want you!
慰めさせてシェイクシェイク
Let me comfort you, Shake Shake.
愛の才能で
With my talent for love.
泣いてくれなきゃ枯れてしまう
If you don't cry for me, I'll wither.
濡れていたいねえいいでしょう？
I want to stay wet, hey, it's okay right?
ダメ取って飲み干したいん
It's no good, I want to drink it all up,
だだだってば
I said D-D-D!
うーわ！
Uwwa!
Fiuh!
Finally done!
Wow.
This way you won't be running away anymore~
Now be good and sit tight okay?
Haa, you really made me work up a sweat.
You make me look for you...
Chase you down...
But I'm just glad that we are finally together again.
Now we get to spend some time together...
Just the two of us.
Ah.
Hey.
Pay attention.
Look at me.
Sini...
Come here...
こっちを見ろよ
Look over here...
Hm. That's a good boy.
I mean that's a good boy~
Alright.
Now that I have your attention,
I can finally show you what I've been working on all this time.
Check this out!
Yay!
今回も誕生日グッズが出ます！
Birthday goods are being released this time too!
Kali ini juga ada merchandise ulang tahun!
This time there is also birthday merchandise!
Ollie akan perkenalkan satu-satu ya.
Ollie will introduce them one by one, okay.
Always think of Ollie Wide Rubber Mat.
You always remember me.
The theme is kinda... looks like a yandere, doesn't it?
But I'm not a yandere, I'm just your girlfriend.
Yeah, it's wide, slightly large size, rubber mat,
recommended for everyday use.
And the illustration is by Hanazawa Akira-sensei!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Okay then the next item will be... こちら！
Okay then the next item will be... This one!
Wow, it's... Hello!
Isn't it so cute? クッションだよ！
Isn't it so cute? It's a cushion!
Bantal, yes. So that when you're sleeping...
Pillow, yes. So that when you're sleeping...
...you remember me. You dream of me.
This... it looks so fluffy.
So I guess better get it for a good night sleep.
Right, and followed by... こちら！
Right, and followed by... This one!
It's a Ring Necklace.
Well it's a ring. If it doesn't fit your size,
then you can just wear it as a necklace.
Isn't that really cool?
そう、これはね、指輪。
So, this is a ring.
でも、サイズが合ってないなら、
But, if the size doesn't fit,
ネックレスでも使える... ことができます。
you can use it... as a necklace too.
Ah... It's so cute.
So make sure that when you go out, you wear this,
so that whenever you go grocery shopping,
no other girls out there will be hitting on you.
Hai, and then we also have... こちら！
Yes, and then we also have... This one!
It's a mug!
Isn't it so cute? I really like the design.
So not only when you're working, or gaming,
or grocery shopping, or uh, sleeping,
but even when you're drinking, you think of me.
And of course, not forgetting... こちら！
And of course, not forgetting... This one!
Situation Voices! In three languages!
In Nihongo!
In Japanese!
In Bahasa Indonesia!
In Indonesian!
And English!
Wow, as always. Sasuga me. Sasuga me.
Wow, as always. Go me. Go me.
はい、そして最後にフルセットをご購入いただいた方には...
Yes, and finally, for those who purchase the full set...
...数量限定で直筆サイン入り...
...a limited quantity will include a handwritten autograph...
...チェキ風ブロマイドカードが付いてきます。
...on a Cheki-style bromide card.
And for those of you guys who buy the full set,
there will be limited edition postcard with my message and my sign.
Ya, jadi bagi yang beli full set-nya itu,
Yes, so for those who buy the full set,
bakal dapet postcard dari Ollie, ada message, ada tanda tangannya juga.
you'll get a postcard from Ollie, with a message and autograph too.
次は通常版... は...
Next, the regular edition... is...
...箔押し複製サイン入り...
...foil-stamped with a reproduced autograph...
...チェキ風ブロマイドカードが付いてきます。
...on a Cheki-style bromide card.
And for those of you who buy like the normal version,
you guys can also get the postcard with my sign and message.
Yang beli versi biasa juga akan dapet postcard
Those buying the regular version will also get a postcard
yang ada message dan sign-nya.
that has a message and sign.
Eugh... Okay. That is all.
That was a mouthful, wasn't it?
But you'll buy my merch, won't you?
Mmm~ That's what I like to hear.
Fuh... Wish I could spend more time with you but...
Unfortunately our time is limited.
Damn.
Sebenernya aku masih mau main sama kamu sih...
Actually I still want to play with you...
Tapi udah waktunya kita berpisah...
But it's time for us to part...
Tapi sebelum itu! Ollie masih ada hadiah buat kamu!
But before that! Ollie still has a gift for you!
Jadi tolong dengarkannya~
So please listen to it~
だからちゃんと聞いてね~
So listen properly, okay?
Don't go anywhere!
こっちを向いて。
Look this way.
声を聞かせて。
Let me hear your voice.
私を見て。
Look at me.
私だけ見て。
Look only at me.
ぞっとした顔が可愛いね
Your horrified face is cute.
君のその身体が欲しいの
I want that body of yours.
あれ？ダニ？ナニ？出会い？ハイ？
Huh? Ticks? What? Meeting? Yes?
可哀想ね君は悪い子なの
Poor thing, you're a bad child.
どの手がお好きで？サ、ニ？サ、ニ？
Which hand do you prefer? 3, 2? 3, 2?
色目が上手で頭沸き？
Good at flirting and crazy in the head?
君に踊らされちゃったアタシは狂う
Made to dance by you, I go crazy.
君の肉まで
Down to your meat,
骨の髄まで
down to the marrow of your bones,
挿れて空っぽになる愛のため
fill it until it's empty, for the sake of love.
胸が苦しいね
My chest hurts,
息が詰まるのね
it's hard to breathe,
それが恋と教えてあげるわ
I'll teach you that that is love.
虚ろな声で
With a hollow voice,
ほら囁いて
come on, whisper,
いい子ね
good boy.
首輪付けた君はラビット
Wearing a collar, you are a Loveit.
イカれちゃったのね
You've gone crazy, haven't you?
恋は盲目ね
Love is blind, isn't it?
したいよね
You want to do it, right?
してあげるわ
I'll do it for you.
居て
Stay.
濡れた君の赤い性液溺れるまで
Until I drown in your wet red fluids.
痛い痛いの飛んで行け死んで詫びるまで
Pain, pain, fly away, until you apologize by dying.
愚か音 愚か音
Foolish sound, foolish sound.
間抜けな顔して
Making such a stupid face.
君は悪い子なの
You're a bad kid, aren't you?
痛いのがお好きで？
Do you like it when it hurts?
さあ煮 さあ煮
Boil it, boil it.
あらお口はチャックで
Oh, zip up your mouth.
何々？
What is it?
性に踊らされちゃう
Being made to dance by your nature.
君はグー
You are 'Goo'!
君の中まで
Deep inside you,
骨の髄まで
down to the marrow of your bones,
しゃぶり尽くせば
if I suck it all dry,
もう空っぽのパペット
you're already an empty puppet.
胸が苦しいね
Your chest hurts, doesn't it?
息が詰まるのね
You can't breathe, can you?
それが恋と教えてあげる
I'll teach you that this is love.
君はピエロね
You are a clown.
愛を囁いて
Whispering of love.
人間の形した
In the shape of a human,
君は誰？
who are you?
イカれちゃったのね
You've gone crazy, haven't you?
恋は盲目ね
Love is blind, isn't it?
したいよね
You want to do it, don't you?
してあげる
I'll do it for you.
吐いて
Spit it out.
報い少ない 汚れ達に溺れるまで
Until you drown in the filth with little reward.
痛い痛いの飛んで行け 息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, go away, until my breath stops.
報い少ない 汚れ達に溺れるまで
Until you drown in the filth with little reward.
痛い痛いの飛んで行け 息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, go away, until my breath stops.
CAST
hololive Indonesia
Kureiji Ollie (holoro)
Vestia Zeta (holoh3ro)
hololive 4th generation
Amane Kanata
hololive English
Takanashi Kiara (Myth)
HOLOSTARS
Minase Rio (UPROAR!!)
Special guest
Michi Mochievee
CREDIT
Thumbnail
k3nzoteruya
3D Animation
OCTOLOID
Tuning, Mix, Mastering
Kururu
Lyric Overlay
Maad
SNS Promotion Assets
Altersky
Choreography
FreeM
Special thanks
トライ フロンティア合同会社
Try Frontier LLC
すくろーす
Sucrose
クックルP
Kukkuru P
aS
合同会社 VESSEL LIFE
VESSEL LIFE LLC
um.
Koudai
Toshiyuki
Thank you so much for coming to watch the 3D Birthday Live!
How was it?
Did you feel my love?
Oh, look at that!
It's the specially prepared bedroom.
Cute, isn't it?
It has a bed, a sofa, Udin...
and, I don't know if you noticed but,
there was a display photo of the people I cherish the most in there.
Did you catch it?
I think the neon stage was really cool too!
You probably spotted a bunch of TVs sitting around.
And, well,
those are there to help me watch you from afar.
Cool, right?
Uh, but come to think of it,
I really did drag you around the stages, huh?
Um, how are you?
Do you feel sick?
Are you okay?
I'm a bit worried but I think it shouldn't affect you too much since I carried you while you were still sleeping.
But- huh? Wha-?
N-No, nothing!
I didn't say anything!
Um, speaking of you,
you kept running and hiding away from me.
Naughty naughty. Tsk, tsk.
You always leave comments and like every post I make,
so I thought you'd like it if I came to visit.
I didn't think it would actually surprise you that much.
Um, I think maybe it was because you were too surprised when I suddenly appeared in front of you?
Yeah... hmm.
But, just so you know,
I worked really hard, just for you.
I practiced my singing,
I sang a lot,
and changed my outfit so many times,
and I wonder if my feelings reached you.
It obviously did, right?
Also, at the end,
I finally managed to catch you.
That's what you hoped for, right?
I mean, 'cause you were running away from me,
because you love me a lot.
Obviously you were expecting it too.
Right?
...Hehe, period!
Anyway, for those of you who are still watching,
thank you by the way,
I have an announcement.
I'll be featured in SO87 song,
Love Me Back,
with a music video!
It's going to be so cool,
so keep an eye out, okay?
Ah... it's just so exciting, isn't it?
If you ever feel the need to feel my love again,
then don't hesitate and please come back to watch the 3D Birthday Live again, okay?
I'll always be here,
waiting for you.
Anyways, bye bye!
Otsu-crazy!
Crazyになるほど恋している ZOMBIE
Lovin' you to the point I'm Crazy ZOMBIE